
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which year was Linkin Park formed?",
    answer: "1999",
    options: [
      "1998",
      "1999",
      "2000",
      "2001"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the name of Linkin Park's debut album?",
    answer: "Hybrid Theory",
    options: [
      "Meteora",
      "Minutes to Midnight",
      "Hybrid Theory",
      "A Thousand Suns"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who was the lead vocalist of Linkin Park?",
    answer: "Chester Bennington",
    options: [
      "Chester Bennington",
      "Mike Shinoda",
      "Brad Delson",
      "Rob Bourdon"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Linkin Park collaborated with Jay-Z on a mash-up album called",
    answer: "Collision Course",
    options: [
      "Hybrid Theory",
      "Collision Course",
      "Reanimation",
      "Meteora"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In which movie did Linkin Park contribute the song 'What I've Done' to the soundtrack?",
    answer: "Transformers",
    options: [
      "The Avengers",
      "Iron Man",
      "Transformers",
      "The Dark Knight"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which album did Linkin Park release in 2017, dedicated to Chester Bennington after his passing?",
    answer: "One More Light",
    options: [
      "One More Light",
      "The Hunting Party",
      "Minutes to Midnight",
      "Living Things"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Where did Linkin Park originate as a band?",
    answer: "Los Angeles, USA",
    options: [
      "New York, USA",
      "Los Angeles, USA",
      "London, UK",
      "Tokyo, Japan"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the title of Linkin Park's third studio album, released in 2007?",
    answer: "Minutes to Midnight",
    options: [
      "One More Light",
      "The Hunting Party",
      "Living Things",
      "Minutes to Midnight"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which Linkin Park song features the lyrics 'I tried so hard and got so far, but in the end, it doesn't even matter'?",
    answer: "In the End",
    options: [
      "Crawling",
      "Numb",
      "In the End",
      "Somewhere I Belong"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which musical genre is Linkin Park associated with primarily?",
    answer: "Metal",
    options: [
      "Metal",
      "Pop",
      "Country",
      "Hip-Hop"
    ]
  }
];